William Dixon

Denver, CO

Full Stack Developer (719)321-3014

Wdixon2186@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/williammdixon/

SKILLS:

Final Cut Pro X, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React Node.js, Express, Bootstrap

PROJECTS:

Trivia: Designed trivia game using HTML, CSS, and Javascript based on famous quotes from wide released movies.

https://wdixon2186.github.io/movieTrivia/

Local Library: worked successfully with NODE.js, Express, Mongoose, HBS, and CSS to build a fully functioning database that housed information on books and movies I own.

https://books-and-movies-db.herokuapp.com/movies

City Fyndr: Worked in a team using Node.js, Express, React.js, Boot-strap, and CSS to develop an app that allows users to find census data on the top 50 cities in the United States.

https://wdixon2186.github.io/City-Search-Front-End/#/

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Caption Call, Colorado Springs, CO

August 2018 – August 2019

Communications Assistant

 Transcribed phone calls for those who are hard of hearing by accessing dragon software, and repeating the conversation.

Torch Middle School, City of Industry, CA

January 2018 - June 2018

Film and Video Volunteer Instructor

- Monitored the safety and completion of 5 different productions including the setting up of lighting, blocking, and camera work.
- Developed and gave lessons on the analytics of different films, and the meanings that can be drawn from different techniques.
- Walked students through the editing software of final cut pro.

PATHFINDER MEDIA, Los Angeles, CA

August 2017 - December

2017

Development Intern

- Managed and evaluated over forty screenplays, including the writing of script coverage.
- Researched and noted potential clients by their previous work and recent successes.

EDUCATION:

Software Engineering Certificate, General Assembly Bachelor of Arts Film Studies, Azusa Pacific University